var golfQuestions = [{
    question: "The player that has the lowest score on a hole, tee's off when, on the next hole?",
    choice: ["first", "last", "second"],
    validAnswer: "first"
}, {
    question: "In golf what does GIR stand for?",
    choice: ["Green in repair", "Green is round", "Green in regulation"],
    validAnswer: "Green in regulation"

}, {
    question: "What is one shot under par?",
    choice: ["par", "birdie", "bogey"],
    validAnswer: "birdie"
}, {
    question: "What is a sand trap?",
    choice: ["A beach", "A hazard", "Out of bounds"],
    validAnswer: "A hazard"
}, {
    question: "How many penalty strokes is a provisional?",
    choice: ["1", "2", "3"],
    validAnswer: "1"
}, {
    question: "What is one shot over par?",
    choice: ["eagle", "birdie", "bogey"],
    validAnswer: "bogey"
}, {
    question: "In golf what does FIR stand for?",
    choice: ["Fairway in Regulation", "Fairway in Repair", "First in Rule"],
    validAnswer: "Fairway in Regulation"
}, {
    question: "How many penalty strokes are given if the player hits the wrong ball?",
    choice: ["1", "2", "3"],
    validAnswer: "2"
}, {
    question: "True or False? You can hit your ball out of a hazard",
    choice: ["true", "false"],
    validAnswer: "true"
}, {
    question: "Which player hits first after hitting from the tee box?",
    choice: ["closest to whole first", "farthest from the hole first", "whoever had the lowest score on the previous hole"],
    validAnswer: "farthest from the hole first"
}
]